class Question
  attr_reader :question, :answer

  def initialize (question, answer) 
    @question = question
    @answer = answer
  end

end


# @questions = [
#   {
#     id: 1,
#     question: "What is 5 * 7",
#     answer: 35,
#   },
#   {
#     id: 2,
#     question: "What is 3 + 2",
#     answer: 5,
#   },
#   {
#     id: 3,
#     question: "What is 6 / 2",
#     answer: 3,
#   },
#   {
#     id: 4,
#     question: "What is 5 * 100",
#     answer: 500,
#   },
#   {
#     id: 5,
#     question: "What is 1 / 1",
#     answer: 1,
#   },
#   {
#     id: 6,
#     question: "What is 2 * 5 * 2",
#     answer: 20,
#   },
#   {
#     id: 7,
#     question: "What is 9 / 3",
#     answer: 3,
#   },
#   {
#     id: 8,
#     question: "What is 50 / 10",
#     answer: 5,
#   },
#   {
#     id: 9,
#     question: "What is 100 / 4",
#     answer: 25,
#   },
#   {
#     id: 10,
#     question: "What is 40 * 4",
#     answer: 160,
#   },
#   {
#     id: 11,
#     question: "What is 3 * 4",
#     answer: 12,
#   },
#   {
#     id: 12,
#     question: "What is 6 + 2 + 2",
#     answer: 10,
#   },
#   {
#     id: 13,
#     question: "What is 12 / 2",
#     answer: 6,
#   },
#   {
#     id: 14,
#     question: "What is 7 * 3",
#     answer: 21,
#   },
#   {
#     id: 15,
#     question: "What is 6 * 9",
#     answer: 54,
#   },
#   {
#     id: 16,
#     question: "What is 2 * 3",
#     answer: 6,
#   },
#   {
#     id: 17,
#     question: "What is 9 + 2",
#     answer: 11,
#   },
#   {
#     id: 18,
#     question: "What is (23 + 3) / 2",
#     answer: 13,
#   },
#   {
#     id: 19,
#     question: "What is 8 * 10 + 1",
#     answer: 81,
#   },
#   {
#     id: 20,
#     question: "What is 1 + 5",
#     answer: 6,
#   },
#   {
#     id: 21,
#     question: "What is 3 * 3 + 2",
#     answer: 11,
#   },
#   {
#     id: 22,
#     question: "What is 4 * 4 + 6",
#     answer: 22,
#   },
#   {
#     id: 23,
#     question: "What is 3 + 2 + 5",
#     answer: 10,
#   },
#   {
#     id: 24,
#     question: "What is (25 - 1) / 12",
#     answer: 2,
#   },
#   {
#     id: 25,
#     question: "What is 3 + 3 + 2",
#     answer: 8,
#   }
# ]
